# Davanjit Sandhu

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

# **OBJECTIVE**

To become a successful web developer with a particular focus on the front-end using any given framework, programming language, or tool. Also, to gain more experience in the field and work on more interesting and challenging projects that I can add to my growing portfolio.

# **EXPERIENCE**

## CHAMPION PRODUCTS CORP. - SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Jan 2024 - Present

Created an application for warehouse workers that monitors employee activity which can then be viewed and downloaded as '.csv' files by the admin. The website uses React.js on the frontend and Node.js/Express.js on the back end as well as a MSSQL database and is hosted on Azure via a 'Dockerized' container. The website also used various Azure services such as the communication API for email, Azure SQL for deploying the database, and Azure blob storage for storing profile pictures and other items.

# MAXX PRINTING - WEBSITE DEVELOPMENT INTERN

Sep 2023 - Jan 2024

I was tasked with creating custom front ends for websites using React.js. Clients would send in their design documents with their custom designs, and I would work on implementing the pages I was assigned. For example, I created custom login pages, custom admin pages, and even custom navigation bars.

## **GAO TEK INC. - SOFTWARE DEVELOPER INTERN**

Aug 2021 - Nov 2021

Worked on various large-scale teams doing various projects such as translating documents relating to VoIP into usable C code and creating pseudo-code for a security feature that would later be added into the project. Got a promotion to a 'team leader' role by the end of my internship where I would have to manage my team and ensure they fulfill their roles.

# CONTACT

Davanjit@hotmail.com (519) 816-8130 Windsor ON, Canada

## LINKS

## Website

http://dav-sandhu.github.io/Personal-Website/

## GitHub

https://github.com/Dav-Sandhu

## LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/davanjit-sandhu-496200211/

# **EDUCATION**

University of Windsor Sep 2016 – June 2021

- Bachelor of Computer Science
- Minor in Political Science

# **SKILLS**

React.js, Node.js, Express.js, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, API's, Docker, Azure, C#, C, C++, Java, Kotlin, Lua, Bootstrap.js, Cypress, Jest, Git, MSSQL, MySQL, MongoDB, Mongoose, AJAX, Redux.js, React Native, Expo, Vite, Unity